https://aroga.com/privacy-policy/

Our Services
What is Lifestyle Medicine?
Our Services
What is Lifestyle Medicine?
Privacy Policy
This policy outlines how we protect the privacy of your personal information and medical record. Everyone working for this office is required to adhere to the protections described in this policy. If you have any questions regarding our privacy practices, please contact your doctor or one of our staff.
Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personal Information
What personal information do we collect?
We collect the following personal information:
Identification and Contact information (name, address, date of birth, emergency contact, etc)
Billing information (provincial plan and/or private insurer)
Health information (symptoms, diagnosis, medical history, test results, reports and treatment, record of allergies, prescriptions, etc)
When and to whom do we disclose personal information?
Implied consent for provision of care: By virtue of seeking care from us, your consent is implied (i.e., assumed) for your information to be used by this office to provide you with care, and to share with other providers involved in your care.
Disclosure to other health care providers: Relevant health information is shared with other providers involved in your care, including (but not limited to) other physicians and specialists, pharmacists, advisers, lab technicians, nutritionists, physiotherapists, occupational therapists.
Disclosures authorized by law: There are limited situations where we are legally required to disclose your personal information without your consent. These situations include (but are not limited to) billing provincial health plans, reporting infectious diseases
For You
Overview
Reversal & Prevention Program
On-Going Monthly Care
For Business
Overview
On-Demand Virtual Care
Executive Assessments
What is Lifestyle Medicine?
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Drop us your email and start receiving our monthly lifestyle medicine newsletter for amazing resources, blogs, education, etc.
Follow Us
©2020 Aroga. All rights reserved.
Term and Conditions
Privacy Policy
